<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Giovanni Alfarizi on Ghur08a</title>
    <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/authors/giovanni-alfarizi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Giovanni Alfarizi on Ghur08a</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:40:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://alfarizi008.github.io/authors/giovanni-alfarizi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trail Running Gears</title>
      <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/trail-running-gears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:40:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/trail-running-gears/</guid>
      <description>What gears should i bring to trail running? It depends the terrain, track, and distance of the route. Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of trail running gear based on Trail and Kale website:
Trail Running Shoes GPS Running Watch Technical Running Cap and Headband / Neck Gaiter Running Hydration Pack (and Water Bottles) Running Sunglasses Running Headlamp Trail Running Poles Wireless Headphones Trail Running Clothes (shirt, shorts, pants, waterproof jacket, sports bra and socks) Trail Running Accessories Trail Running Nutrition How Running Trail Terrain and Climate Influences Your Choice of Trail Running Gear The list above is optional based on the needs of the runner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trail Running</title>
      <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/trail-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:07:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/trail-running/</guid>
      <description>What is trail running? Quote from Salomon websites:
Trail running is simply defined as going for a run in the heart of nature. It&amp;rsquo;s an extremely all-round non-stadia sport that, of course, works the legs, but also the upper body. Lastly, it requires concentration and attention.
Usually the track of trail running includes ascent and descents, rough terrain, hills, and many more so it make the sport more interesting yet challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different Types of Vaccine in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-vaksin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 13:09:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-vaksin/</guid>
      <description>The types of COVID-19 vaccines used in Indonesia are those produced by PT Bio Farma, Oxford-AstraZeneca, Sinopharm, Moderna, Novavax, Pfizer-BioNTech, and Sinovac.
1. Oxford-AstraZeneca The Oxford-AstraZeneca COVID-19 vaccine is a recombinant adenoviral vector vaccine. Quoted from Very Well Health, recombinant vaccines use a small portion of the genetic material of a pathogen, such as SARS-CoV-2, to trigger an immune response.
Certain parts of the virus can be targeted and these vaccines are generally safe to use in large populations of people even those with chronic health problems or people with impaired immunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different Types of Bicycle</title>
      <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-sepeda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:29:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-sepeda/</guid>
      <description>Folding Bike Characteristics : compact, light and flexible
User type : murban society with high mobility
Place of use : urban street
Mountain Bike Characteristics : tough structure, with suspension fork
User type : outdoor activity lover
Place of use : forest, mountains
Roadbike Characteristics : tough and light structure, curved handlebar, acceleration features
User type : bicycle sports lovers, long-distance use
Place of use : paved road
Rodster Bicycle Characteristics : vintage design, rear seat, signature fender</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different Types of Pasta</title>
      <link>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:29:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://alfarizi008.github.io/posts/jenis-jenis-pasta/</guid>
      <description>What is pasta? Pasta is a processed food used in Italian cuisine, which is usually made from a dough not made from durum wheat flour (semolina) mixed with air or eggs and formed into sheets or various shapes, which are then cooked or baked. .
Perhaps the most familiar we encounter is macaroni. Yup, macaroni is a type of pasta that is widely known by the people of Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
